seventymm.com 2009-02-07

# Seventymm | Privacy Policy

Browse Movies

Popular Rentals

Isko Nahi Dekha Toh Kya Dekha

Special This Month

Award Winners

| | | |   
---|---|---  
| 

Please read our Privacy Policy, so as to understand the terms involved in your subscribing to our service, and how we use the personal information you submit. As we update and expand our services, this policy may change, so we recommend that you refer to it periodically.

Background

When you register at Seventymm™, we ask you for personal information. We use this information to process your orders and to communicate with you about the status of your orders. We also use your email address to send you messages about Seventymm™ special offers, promotional announcements and consumer surveys. Occasionally, we send our customers special offers and promotional information via postal mail, using the shipping address provided. For additional information please email us at [support@seventymm.com](mailto:customerservice@seventymm.com).

Collection and Use of Information

When you first register at Seventymm™, we ask for your email address and a password. When you place your first order for the Seventymm™ Service, we ask you for your full name, physical address, telephone number, your preferred mode of payment so we can dispatch your order. You must certify that you are at least 18 years old. (People under 18 cannot use Seventymm™'s services.) Our server stores this information so that placing future orders will be quicker and easier. If you want to update your address or change credit cards, go to "My Account" and make the appropriate changes. You must be signed in to access "My Account". We also track your order so you can access My Account and immediately determine which VCDs and DVDs you've ordered.

Email Options

We use email from time to time to update you on the latest promotions, special discounts, etc., that we may offer to our members. We also use email to reply to your queries that you may have from time to time.

You can always access the personal information you have provided to Seventymm™ by going to the link "My Account". You can make changes to this information to update your account any time.

Disclosure

Except as described in this section, we will not sell, rent or disclose your personally identifying information to third parties without notifying you of our intent to share the information and giving you an opportunity to prevent your information from being shared. We occasionally use other companies, agents or contractors to perform services necessary to our operations. For example, we have partnered with other companies to personalize our Web pages, process payment transactions, analyze customers' interaction with our site and process consumer surveys. We also provide postal addresses to the Courier Service for delivery purposes. In the course of providing such services, these companies may have contact with your personally identifying information. We will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies. From time to time, we may partner with companies whose products we believe will interest our members. In conjunction with these partners, we occasionally send promotional announcements to particular members. We do not automatically include our members in any particular marketing promotion; instead, we use a variety of factors, including member activity at the Seventymm™ site, to determine the appropriate members. We may use a vendor to carry out these mailings. However, the partner company does not have access to your email address or any other information that could identify you or be used to contact you directly. Seventymm™ also reserves the right to disclose information when required by law. We also provide analyses of our members in the aggregate to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties. We do this so that we, and our advertisers can understand you better, and so we can keep bringing you the best services. We may also disclose, on an anonymous basis, literal statements made by our members. At no time, however, will we disclose personal information about specific members. Members should check back for updates to this policy.

Security and Access

You can access "My Account" from every page on the site to update and correct your name, email address, password, postal address, credit cards, etc., Please note that you must be signed in to Seventymm™ to access this information. We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technologies become available. We make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system.

|   
| |
